var questions = [
    {
	question: 'Which is a towering staue of Jesus Christ?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Christ Redeemer'],
    },
    {
	question: 'Which is located in Peru?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Machu Picchu'],
    },
    {
	question: '10 + 10 = ?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Chichen Itza'],
    },
    {
	question: '15 - 7 = ?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Chichen Itza'],
    },
    {
	question: 'Which took more than 22,000 people to build?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Taj Mahal'],
    },
    {
	question: 'Which houses over 800 tombs?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Petra'],
    },
    {
	question: 'Which was built by soldiers, peasants, convicts and war prisoners?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Great Wall of China'],
    },
    {
	question: 'Which could hold about 50,000 people?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Colosseum'],
    },
    {
	question: 'Which is incorrectly thought to seen from space unaided?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Great Wall of China'],
    },
    {
	question: 'Which has a very popular treasury?',
	options: ['Christ Redeemer', 'Great Wall of China', 'Petra', 'Colosseum', 'Chichen Itza', 'Machu Picchu', 'Taj Mahal'],
	answer: ['Petra'],
    },
];